Guide to the Carl Feiss papers, [ca.1928]-1991
Feiss, Carl papers, [ca.1928]-1991
- Series II. Professional Papers
  - Projects
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: correspondence., 1967-1969 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: "Study Design," monthly report, notes, preliminary questionnaire, "Regional Problems and Opportunities.", 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: correspondence, mostly with Don King, Executive Director, Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council., 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: memoranda, mostly from King., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: "Planning and Development in the Region.", 1967 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Tampa, Florida; Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: "Application for Urban Planning Assistance Grant.", 1967 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: draft of "Analysis of Development Factors.", 1967 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: draft of "Analysis of Development Factors.", 1967 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: Tampa Bay Planner, January-December 1971. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: Council of Governments: brochure, notes, "Bipartisan Support for the Council of Governments," "Council of Governments: What and Why Are They?" "St. Petersburg Area Chamber of Commerce Community Development," corrsepondence., 1967 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: clippings, maps, "City Hall," "Summary Report on the Status of the Newly Created TBRPC.", 1962-1966 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: correspondence, memoranda., 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: correspondence re: payment to Feiss for professional services., 1966 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: correspondence, "A Regional Plan for Outdoor Recreation Facilities in the Tampa Bay Area.", 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: list of officers, membership and staff; resumes; list of applicants for the position of Executive Director., 1966 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: "Application for Urban Planning Assistance Grant.", 1966 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Bay Regional Planning Council: accounts of expenses, correspondence re: expenses., 1966-1971 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Timberlake: "An Appraisal of the Industrial Development Potential for Timberlake, Including an Industry Acquisition Program," "Demand Analysis for Recreation Development in the Tellico Reservoir Region.", 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Timberlake: "Recreation Development Plan for the Tellico Reservoir.", 1973 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Timberlake: clippings, House Resolution no. 13, "Excerpts from survey conducted in February 1972 by Political Surveys and Analysis, Inc.," "Timberlake Evaluation and Planning Study," "Guidelines for the Provision of Facilities and Services for Timberlake Residents," "Timberlake City: 1972 Program Forumlation: Working Paper Number 1972-I, II.", 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Timberlake: "Industrial Potential: The Timberlake New Community East-Central Tennessee Contract," "Report on Timberlake, Tennessee.", 1972-1973. (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: "Environmental Statement: Volume I.", 1972 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: "Environmental Statement: Volume II.", 1972 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: "Environmental Statement: Volume III.", 1972 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: TVA organizational tree; correspondence with James L. Gober, Regional Planning Staff; "The Tennessee Valley Authority's Tellico Project.", 1972 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: "Timberlake: History and Culture," "Cherokees Along the Little Tennessee," "Final Environmental Statement: Tellico Project.", 1972 [?] (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: memorandum, notes, clippings, proceedings of Environmental Defense Fund, et al. v. Tennessee Authority, et al., 1971 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Annual Report., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Timberlake: correspondence re: renewal of Feiss' contract., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Timberlake: "A Preliminary Planning Report.", 1969 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: "Informal Summary of the Meetings of April 22-23, 1969," map, correspondence. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: contract, correspondence., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - [empty] (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: "?summary report of observations on Tellico plans to date.", 1968 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: Tellico Project: photographs, notes, "Tellico New Community: A Proposal," "Tellico Planning," correspondence., 1968 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority: accounts of expenses, contract, material on Memphis., 1967-1970 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Thomasville Landmarks: Thomasville, Georgia: correspondence with Norman C. Larson, Executive Director., 1972 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Thomasville Landmarks: Thomasville, Georgia: Oak Leaves, July 1970-April 1972; correspondence., 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Thomasville Landmarks: Thomasville, Georgia: "Historic Thomasville: An Inventory of Historic Buildings and Sites: Program Recommendations.", 1969 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Thomasville Landmarks: Thomasville, Georgia: photographs of Greenwood Plantation, maps of Thomasville, "The Health Resort." (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Thomasville Landmarks: Thomasville, Georgia: "Report to Thomasville Landmarks, Inc.," notes, correspondence., 1967-1969 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - United States Housing Authority: correspondence, "Instructions Covering Preparation of Statements by USHA Consultants in Making Claim for Salary.", 1939 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: demonstration study, correspondence, position paper, resolutions, clippings., 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - [empty] (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "Plan and Program for the Preservation of the Vieux Carre.", 1968 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, including report., 1968 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "Vieux Carre Demonstration Grant Study: Final Report Draft.", 1968 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, draft and revisions of "Vieux Carre Demonstration Grant Study.", 1968 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: corespondence, drafts of "Vieux Carre Demonstration Grant Study.", 1968 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: memoranda, "Report of the Technical Committee Relative to the Draft of the Final Report on the Vieux Carre Demonstration Grant Study," "Report on Historic Areas and Structures: Community Renewal Program Study," "Summary of the Legal and Administrative Aspects," Bureau of Government Research 1967 Annual Report, correspondence. (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: draft of Vieux Carre Report, notes., 1967 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, "Administration Report.", 1967 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - [empty] (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "An Evaluation of the Effects of the Proposed Riverfront Expressway on the Vieux Carre, New Orleans, Louisiana.", 1966 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: draft of "An Evaluation of the Effects of the Proposed Riverfront Expressway on the Vieux Carre, New Orleans, Louisiana.", 1966 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "A History of the Plan of the Vieux Carre.", 1966 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - [empty] (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, notes, "Application for Grant Extension, Vieux Carre Demonstration Grant Study, no. La. D-2.", 1966 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence with Louis E. Newman, Bureau of Governmental Research, including summary reports., 1966 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: work papers., 1966 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "Proposal to Expand the Scope of the Vieux Carre Demonstration Study to Provide for Additional Studies Relating to the Proposed Riverfront Expressway," "Working Paper 8: Summation of Building Ratings," "The Vieux Carre as an Administrative Area," "A Design Study for the Proposed Riverfront Expressway," "Working Paper 7: An Analysis of Recent Development," "Study of the Proposed Riverfront and Elysian Fields Expressway and an Alternate Proposal.", 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence with Louis Newman, Director, Bureau of Governmental Research, including work programs., 1965 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: clippings, memoranda, "Working Paper 1: Inventory Maps.", 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "Demonstration Grant Application, Pages 9 through 16 and Work Schedule Chart.", 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence, clippings, progress reports, "Proposal for a Traffic Study Related to the Waterfront Expressway.", 1965 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: notes, correspondence., 1965 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: Arkitekten 4, 1964; clippings; "Vieux Carre Survey;" notes; brochure for "New Orleans International Exhibition Facility;" "Notes from C.R.P. Application;" "Statement Prepared for Public Hearing Regarding the Riverside Expressway in New Orleans Held on March 24;" "1965 Work Program Proposals;" "Report of 1964 Activities;" "Notes Regarding the Development of the Riverfront-Elysian Fields Expressway and the Role of the Central Area Committee.", 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: "Guidelines for Growth in Central New Orleans: Recommendations for the General Plan.", 1965 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - [empty] (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: clippings; Vieux Carre Property Owners and Associates, Inc. News Bulletin, April 1965; "Through Portals of the Past," New Orleans survey," "Draft of Vieux Carre Demonstration Grant Application to HHFA," "Vieux Carre Commission," "The Vieux Carre Commission: Its Purpose and Function," "Subdivision Regulations," notes; "Economic Survey of the Central Area of New Orleans," demolition ordinances, "Laws and Ordinances Regulating and Affecting the Vieux Carre." (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence., 1965 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Vieux Carre: New Orleans, Louisiana: correspondence., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Virgin Islands: "General Plan of the Virgin Islands.", 1969 [?] (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Virgin Islands: correspondence; clippings; Your Washington Report, August 1969, December 1969. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Virgin Islands: Department of Housing and Community Renewal Annual Report 1966-1967; maps; "Master Plan for the Virgin Islands: A Course in City and Regional Planning, College of the Virgin Islands;" tourist brochures; "State of the Territory Message, January 22, 1968;" Virgin Islands View, December 1967; notes, "College of the Virgin Islands Progress Report: Title I of the Higher Education Act of 1965, The Virgin Islands;" clippings, list of addresses and phone numbers; published proceedings of the Seventh Legislature of the Virgin Islands.", 1966-1968 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Virgin Islands: correspondence with Ralph M. Paiewonksy, Governor, Virgin Islands; notes., 1967 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Virgin Islands: clippings, "Report on Relocation of Displaced Families Under the Projected Urban Renewal Program in the U.S. Virgin Islands," "Community Renewal Program: U.S. Virgin Islands: Final Report and Long-Range Recommendations.", 1965-1968 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Virgin Islands: notes; federal legislation and regulation; America's Lifelines: Federal Aid for Highways, January 1966., 1933-1961 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Virgin Islands: "Conference Report," "Federal Laws, Regulations, and Other Material Relating to Highways.", 1960, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Virgin Islands: "Outdoor Recreation Grants-in-Aid Manual," "Obtaining Money to Conserve Land," correspondence, "Grants for Public Outdoor Recreation," order form for "Outdoor Recreation Grants-in-Aid Manual," notes, "Open Space Project: A Summary Report.", 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Virgin Islands: notes, work programs, brochures for Virgin Island businesses., 1964 [?] (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Virgin Islands: Virgin Islands Planning Board: "A proposed ordinance creating an architectural control district and historic architecture sites and places, and establishing regulations for their preservation and protection; and providing for the creation of a board of architectural review," Annual Report 1967, memoranda, "Final Report and Summary of Long-Range Recommendations for the Community Renewal Program for the U.S. Virgin Islands," clippings, "Taarneberg-Ross Estate: Proposed Renewal Project," "Building Code," "Act no. 801: Act to Provide for Zoning and Subdivisions in the Virgin Islands, and for Other Purposes.", 1966 [?] (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Virgin Islands: "Bill no. 2011: Act to Amend Chapter 5, Title 29, Virgin Islands Code," "Bill no. 2698: To Approve the Rules and Regulations Issued Under the Building Code," blank U.S. census questionnaires., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Virgin Islands: contract for Feiss' professional services (with Nathaniel S. Keith)., 1966 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Virgin Islands: correspondence., 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - RESTRICTED: Oral history interview with Charles B. Hosmer, Jr. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - RESTRICTED: Oral history interview with Kermit C. Parsons (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Capitol Center Planning Commission: Florida: correspondence, "Brief History and Chronology of Capitol Center Planning," plans of Florida Capitol Center, "Analysis of Capitol Center Planning Act, clippings., 1969-1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - "City of Jasper, Florida Central Business District Revitalization Proposals.", 1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Council of State Planning Agencies: Fourth Annual Conference of Regional Councils, March 15-18, 1970: program, correspondence; Fifth Annual Conference of Regional Councils, March 7-10, 1971: announcement, program; Metropolitan and Regional Planning Agencies: "Proposed Funding Levels for CPA Program;" "Metropolitan Functional Authorities," correspondence., 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Ditchley Foundation: Anglo-American Conference on New Towns, November 15-18, 1968: list of members, correspondence, "Report of Group ?A:' Planning and Building New Towns," program, notes, "revised amendments to nominal lists," "terms of reference," "Background Paper on New Towns Experience in Great Britain," procedural notes, "Working Group A: To consider further problems of planning and building new towns," "Working Group B: To consider further problems of finance and administration of new towns," "Working Group C: To consider further social problems in the development in new towns," "Notes for the Guidance of Chairmen and Rapporteurs and for the information of other members of Groups at Ditchley Conference," "Documentation," maps of "New Towns of Great Britain," clippings, booklet on Ditchley Foundations, "Planning and Evolution," "Investigating Cumbernauld New Town: A factual guide for every organization face with development programs." (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - National Housing Conference, Washington, D.C., December 1, 1969: "Proposed Resolutions." (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, Maryland: notes, program statement, budget., 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, Maryland: notes., 1970 [?] (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Beaufort, South Carolina: Architectural Inentory., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Busch Properties, Inc.: Kingsmill: correspondence, "Articles of Incorporation," bylaws, meeting minutes, "Preliminary Candidate Presentation for Richard G. Knight," resumes, builders agreement, "Declaration of Covenants and Restrictions," "Amendment to Declaration of Covenants and Restrictions," "Purchaser's Guide to Homebuilding at Kingsmill," plans, "Florida Public Offering Statement," "Buyer's Guide to Littletown Quarter.", 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Busch Properties, Inc.: Kingsmill: "Buyer's Guide to Winster Fax," advertising materials, correspondence, plans, clippings., 1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Busch Properties, Inc.: Kingsmill: maps, charts., 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Busch Properties, Inc.: Kingsmill: contract for Feiss; professional services., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Durham, North Carolina: "Development Controls and Procedures in the Durham, North Carolina Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area.", 1968 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Durham, North Carolina: correspondence, "Central Business District Redevelopment Plan.", 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Durham, North Carolina: plans, correspondence, "Final Project Report.", 1964 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Durham, North Carolina: draft of "Project Report.", 1963 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - East Central Florida Regional Planning Council: memoranda, "Regional Background for Planning the Coastal Area.", 1968 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Falls of the Ohio: "Metropolitan Council of Governments, 701 Application.", 1967 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: meeting minutes, Annual Report 1971, correspondence, memoranda, budget, "Overall Program Design.", 1972-1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: notes, "Annual Work Program," "Interim Urban Area Plan," "Approved Work Program," organizational tree, "Application for Planning Grant," meeting minutes, "Reports of Workshop Deliberations.", 1971 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: correspondence., 1971 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: The Mid-Cumberland Compendium, October 1970-May 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: brochure, correspondence, "Application for Urban Planning Grant.", 1969 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: contract with Barge, Waggoner, and Sumner, Inc.; "A program outline for improving the economic prospects of metropolitan Nashville, using local business and leadership as an action group and the Nashville area Chamber of Commerce as a control and co-ordinating point," "Bibliography of Development Publications," "Nashville-Davidson County and Regional Development Patterns.", 1968 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: meeting minutes, memoranda, correspondence, announcement of public lectures, clippings, "A Two-Year Work Program: Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments: Report and Recommendations," "A Statistical Profile of the Middle Tennessee Regional Conference," schedule of meetings, budgets., 1968-1969 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments and Mid-Cumberland Development District: Tennessee: contract with Feiss for professional services, correspondence, introduction to report on "the status of planning operations within the nine-county area comprising the Mid-Cumberland Council of Governments," planning commission reports, budget, regional plan., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): "Schedule for Review and Completion of Comprehensive Planning Assistance Project no. Tenn. P-115: Study Design," correspondence re: "Comprehensive Planning Assistance Program Agency Personnel Procedures," "An Application for an Urban Planning Assistance Project Grant.", 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): correspondence, "Agreement MATCOG and Carl Feiss, Comprehensive Contract no. Tenn. P-115(G)., 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): correspondence., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): memoranda, notes and abstract for "Final Report, Five-Year Work Program Design for the MATCOG.", 1970 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): correspondence, "Five-Year Housing Program for the MATCOG," "Initial Housing Element for MATCOG," "Work Element 6: Housing Program," memoranda., 1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): Memphis: correspondence, maps, visitors' guide., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): presentation transparencies, Annual Report, clippings, "Mid-South Center Council for Comprehensive Health Planning," "Metropolitan Memphis: Its Facilities, Its Services," notes, "Metropolitan Memphis: Its Financial Profile," meeting minutes, "Report of the Joint Committee to Investigate State House Needs.", 1969 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): working outline, correspondence, charts., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): "Study Design for a Five-Year Work Program for the MATCOG: Summary Report," "Proposed Basic Budget and Staff.", 1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - MATCOG (Mississippi-Arkansas-Tennessee Council of Governments): maps: Nashville, Official Local Planning Commissions; list of members., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Nationwide Insurance: Columbus, Ohio: notes, maps, brochures, clippings, "Brief Summary: Proposed Development Program for Downtown Columbus, 1965-1975," map of "Columbus Central Core," "Manual of Procedure," list of conferences., 1964-1965 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Palm Beach County: Area Planning Board: "Working Paper no. 1: Palm Beach County as Seen by Residents," "Working Paper no. 2: Planning Area Profiles.", 1969 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Palm Beach County: Area Planning Board: "Contract for Personal Services, Urban Planning Assistance Project Area Planning Board, Palm Beach County.", 1967 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Piedmont Triad Council of Governments: map, notes, discussion outline, "Planning Officials' Views," "Priorities for Development: A Survey," "Anderson contract," "Horton contract," work schedule., 1969 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Puerto Rico: correspondence, "Relamento de Zonificacion Proyecto de Enmienda," draft., 1968 (Box 39, Folder 15)